

<u>Shivam Vishwakarma</u>

Senior Software Engineer

My Contact



shivamvish160@gmail.com



+918887516560



Hyderabad, Telangana

Hard Skill

- ServiceNow
- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS
- Angular

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

National Institute of Technology, Durgapur

B.Tech in Mechanical Engineering

Completed in 2021

Certifications

Certified Implementation Specialist CSM

Certified Application Developer CAD

Achievements

2021 - 2022 Received Applause Award

2022 - 2023 Received Spot Award

About Me

I have 3.5+ years of experience, specializing in delivering solutions using the ServiceNow platform. My work focuses on the Service Portal, ITSM module, CSM module and enhancing service delivery and user experience. I earned my degree from the National Institute of Technology (NIT), Durgapur, which has equipped me with a solid technical foundation.

Professional Experience

Jade Global | Senior Software Engineer February 2024 - Present

1)-HealthScan (ServiceNow)

I ensure code follows ServiceNow best practices, enhance definitions, analyze issues, support users, and implement business logic. I work with my team and take full responsibility for assigned modules.

Deloitte USI | Business Technology Analyst June 2021 - February 2024

1)-Regulated Products(GPS):

Developed Web application to provide license to states to sell marijuana basically in out of India

We developed complete licensing process, starting from applying to approval of license and also if licensee doesn't obey the rules of license issued for him then state can take action against the license by creating a violation tickets against him. These all capabilities we implemented using CSM module of ServiceNow, CSM configurable workspace and Service portal with angular js.

2)-FedEx:

We developed complete tracking of a package from pickup to delivery by using CSM module of ServiceNow Which also includes approval based on cost of packages.

We also worked on CSM configurable workspace to show dashboards to various personas based on there roles.

3)-Kreator:

In this project we have created forms directly which was already created by end users by drag and drop in kreator tool. We integrated kreator tool with ServiceNow and once end user is done with there form on kreator tool using drag drop functionality and they submit the form then a form get's created in ServiceNow automatically with accurate positioning and CSS which reduces lot of efforts of developer.